<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
	<title>Shroom Kingdom</title>
	<subtitle>Shroom Kingdom is an upcoming play-to-earn earn video game built with web technologies running on the NEAR Blockchain.</subtitle>
	<link href="https://shroomkingdom.net/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
  <link href="https://shroomkingdom.net"/>
	<generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
	<updated>2021-10-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
	<id>https://shroomkingdom.net/atom.xml</id>
	<entry xml:lang="en">
		<title>Shroom Kingdom Roadmap</title>
		<published>2021-10-01T00:00:00+00:00</published>
		<updated>2021-10-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<link href="https://shroomkingdom.net/blog/roadmap/" type="text/html"/>
		<id>https://shroomkingdom.net/blog/roadmap/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the roadmap of the Shroom Kingdom project.
Our goal is to give you a brief overview on what you can and what you cannot expect me to deliver in the near future and give you a better understanding on what I need help for the most.
I started this project solely on my own and with the help of the NEAR-Team I got this far already.
Are you willing to become part of the Shroom-Kingdom family?
Hit me up with your ideas!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;span id=&quot;continue-reading&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;h2 id=&quot;topics&quot;&gt;Topics&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A quick look at what needs and needed to be done as a whole:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot; checked=&quot;&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Deciding on which ecosystem the game is going to be built&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot; checked=&quot;&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Sharing the idea in this ecosystem and setting up social media accounts&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot; checked=&quot;&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Connecting with people to build a community that participate in the project&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Deciding on the economics of the token&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Launching the token via DAO community vote&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Creating hype through airdrops and starting to reward early supporters&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Distributing tasks within the community&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Setting up the legal framework for the financial ecosystem&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Launching the token through an IDO&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Creating incentives for people to stick around and be curious about the project&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Creating in-game-design and on-chain art (NFTs)&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Developing the actual game&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&quot;&quot; type=&quot;checkbox&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
Creating mechanisms to avoid fraud &#x2F; cheating and other misbehaviours&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;deciding-on-which-ecosystem-the-game-is-going-to-be-built&quot;&gt;Deciding on which ecosystem the game is going to be built&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any important aspect of how we wanna build the game is how the ecosystem and with it the amount of community support.
It&#x27;s way more important than technical aspects of the network, everything can be improved later on when you work with the right people. That&#x27;s why I decided to choose the NEAR ecosystem.
Its main purpose is to strengthen community and create games with a different approach than conventional games.
People get supported with a vision and people that are experts in all kinds of field are able to help people from a hobby-developer to a full-time-gaming dev.
With such a strong community where people use their strengths to each others&#x27; advantage, it&#x27;s way easier to make my vision a reality.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;sharing-the-idea-in-this-ecosystem-and-setting-up-social-media-accounts&quot;&gt;Sharing the idea in this ecosystem and setting up social media accounts&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One day after I set up my social media accounts, specifically Twitter and Github, I got a very interesting Email from &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;humanguild.io&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Humanguild&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.
They were asking me, if I would be interested to talk about my idea with them and how they might be able to help me.
I am absolutely amazed what great work they are doing in supporting projects that build on NEAR Protocol in such an early phase.
They give me a lot of trust even though I just started with an idea.
I think this demonstrates the spirit of Web3 and what great people work in there.
Humanguild helps me especially with content creation and connecting with the right people.
Ever since then I learned a lot about the NEAR ecosystem, which would have taken longer without them.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;connecting-with-people-to-build-a-community-that-participate-in-the-project&quot;&gt;Connecting with people to build a community that participate in the project&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was time to create a DAO around the game, to find people that are willing to take the risk of spending their time to help me in exchange for a potentially worthless token if the game doesn&#x27;t get any traction. I made my mind up about economic incentives and thought about the first few tasks people could support me with while there was not too much to work with, yet&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;deciding-on-the-economics-of-the-token&quot;&gt;Deciding on the economics of the token&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a work in progress right now.
I have an overall idea of how I want it to be set up and how tokens are supposed to be distributed within the IDO and amongst DAO-members, but the specifics of the in-game contents are still being discussed.
We all are open for any form of contribution of ideas of what makes sense and how people can have the most fun and are incentivised to stay.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;launching-the-token-via-dao-community-vote&quot;&gt;Launching the token via DAO community vote&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will soon launch our SHRM token via a DAO community vote, using &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;v2.sputnik.fund&#x2F;#&#x2F;shrm.sputnik-dao.near&quot;&gt;SputnikDAO&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.
It will be fundamental milestone and if you want to participate, you can contact me on our &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;discord.gg&#x2F;SPZsgSe&quot;&gt;Discord server&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.
You can read more about the SHRM token in &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;whitepaper.shroomkingdom.net&#x2F;&quot;&gt;our whitepaper&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;creating-hype-through-airdrops-and-starting-to-reward-early-supporters&quot;&gt;Creating hype through airdrops and starting to reward early supporters&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will launch a token airdrop and I think it is a great idea to support NEAR early adopters.
I got this idea from the official &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;gov.near.org&#x2F;t&#x2F;token-airdrops-from-new-projects-of-near-ecosystem-to-near-early-supporters&#x2F;184&quot;&gt;NEAR forums&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; and I think other projects should do so as well.
This is why I have been working on a backend to find eligible accounts for an airdrop.
The backend is based on &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;stats.gallery&#x2F;&quot;&gt;stats.gallery&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.
I implemented additional methods for easily querying such accounts and you can directly check below, whether you will be eligible for our upcoming token airdrop.
The database might still sync with the NEAR indexer and it will take some time until your account shows up.
You can also check your stats on stats.gallery, since it should be the same.
Based on the level you have reached, more tokens will be directly dropped to your wallet after we have launched the token and finished all preparations to do so.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
  var createdBeforeThreshold = new Date(&#x27;2021-10-01&#x27;);
  var createdBefore = false;
  var createdAt = null
  var stakedOnce = false;
  var levelReached = false;
  var level = null;
  var ok = false;
  var syncing = false;
  async function onClick() {
    if (syncing) return;
    const { value } = document.querySelector(&#x27;#near-name&#x27;);
    if (!value) return;

    const inputOk = document.querySelector(&#x27;#check-ok&#x27;);
    const inputCreated = document.querySelector(&#x27;#check-created&#x27;);
    const inputStaked = document.querySelector(&#x27;#check-stake&#x27;);
    const inputLevel = document.querySelector(&#x27;#check-level&#x27;);

    inputOk.src = &quot;images&#x2F;sync.svg&quot;
    syncing = true;
    const res = await fetch(`https:&#x2F;&#x2F;stats.shroomkingdom.net&#x2F;mainnet&#x2F;score-query?account_id=${value}`);
    await new Promise(resolve =&gt; setTimeout(resolve, 1000));
    syncing = false;
    if (!res.ok) return;
    const json = await res.json();
    if (json.length === 0) {
      inputCreated.src = &quot;images&#x2F;error.svg&quot;
      inputStaked.src = &quot;images&#x2F;error.svg&quot;
      inputLevel.src = &quot;images&#x2F;error.svg&quot;
      inputOk.src = &quot;images&#x2F;error.svg&quot;
      return;
    }
    const { created_at_block_timestamp, stake, level: levelRes } = json[0];
    if (created_at_block_timestamp) {
      createdAt = new Date(created_at_block_timestamp &#x2F; 1000000);
      createdBefore = createdAt.valueOf() &lt;= createdBeforeThreshold;
    }
    stakedOnce = stake;
    levelReached = levelRes &gt;= 3;
    level = levelRes;
    ok = createdBefore &amp;&amp; stakedOnce &amp;&amp; levelReached;
    if (createdBefore) {
      inputCreated.src = &quot;images&#x2F;check.svg&quot;
    } else {
      inputCreated.src = &quot;images&#x2F;error.svg&quot;
    }
    if (stakedOnce) {
      inputStaked.src = &quot;images&#x2F;check.svg&quot;
    } else {
      inputStaked.src = &quot;images&#x2F;error.svg&quot;
    }
    if (levelReached) {
      inputLevel.src = &quot;images&#x2F;check.svg&quot;
    } else {
      inputLevel.src = &quot;images&#x2F;error.svg&quot;
    }
    if (ok) {
      inputOk.src = &quot;images&#x2F;check.svg&quot;
    } else {
      inputOk.src = &quot;images&#x2F;error.svg&quot;
    }
  }
&lt;&#x2F;script&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;label&gt;Your NEAR account name: &lt;&#x2F;label&gt;
&lt;input class=&quot;input&quot; id=&quot;near-name&quot; &#x2F;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;button class=&quot;check primary button&quot; onclick=&quot;onClick()&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img id=&quot;check-ok&quot; src=&quot;images&#x2F;pending.svg&quot; &#x2F;&gt;
  Check eligibility
&lt;&#x2F;button&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;label class=&quot;label&quot;&gt;&lt;img id=&quot;check-created&quot; src=&quot;images&#x2F;pending.svg&quot; &#x2F;&gt;Created before 2021-10-01&lt;&#x2F;label&gt;
&lt;label class=&quot;label&quot;&gt;&lt;img id=&quot;check-stake&quot; src=&quot;images&#x2F;pending.svg&quot; &#x2F;&gt;Has staked at least once (directly or via Metapool)&lt;&#x2F;label&gt;
&lt;label class=&quot;label&quot;&gt;&lt;img id=&quot;check-level&quot; src=&quot;images&#x2F;pending.svg&quot; &#x2F;&gt;Has reached level 3&lt;&#x2F;label&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What&#x27;s special about this airdrop is, that you don&#x27;t have to do anything to receive it.
We will just drop it into your wallet via a DAO vote.
You just have to make sure to be eligible.
There are two additional requirements for eligibility, which are:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;it needs to be a named .near account&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;it needs to be a top level account, not a sub account like contract.name.near, because they are commonly used for deploying contracts&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally to the token airdrop, we are also preparing an NFT airdrop as we explained in our &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;shroomkingdom.net&#x2F;blog&#x2F;nft-airdrop&#x2F;&quot;&gt;previous blog post&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.
We are still in preparation phase and are collaborating with artists.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	<entry xml:lang="en">
		<title>Founder NFT</title>
		<published>2021-09-08T00:00:00+00:00</published>
		<updated>2021-09-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<link href="https://shroomkingdom.net/tasks/founder-nft/" type="text/html"/>
		<id>https://shroomkingdom.net/tasks/founder-nft/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We just recently announced our upcoming &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;shroomkingdom.net&#x2F;blog&#x2F;nft-airdrop&#x2F;&quot;&gt;NFT Airdrop&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It will be possible for participants of the Airdrop to acquire a special Founder NFT,
which can be displayed in our &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;app.shroomkingdom.net&#x2F;&quot;&gt;web application&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.
The NFT will also unlock &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;near-chan.github.io&#x2F;&quot;&gt;NEAR chan&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; as a playable character.
All artwork should be submitted either as PNG or losless WebP.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	<entry xml:lang="en">
		<title>NFT Airdrop announcement</title>
		<published>2021-09-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
		<updated>2021-09-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<link href="https://shroomkingdom.net/blog/nft-airdrop/" type="text/html"/>
		<id>https://shroomkingdom.net/blog/nft-airdrop/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hey all!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#x27;ve been thinking a lot in our DAO (btw you can join us. Just visit our &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;discord.gg&#x2F;SPZsgSe&quot;&gt;Discord server&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;)
how we should make early advertisement as good as possible.
Many blockchain projects, who also distribute their own token, launch an Airdrop as a cheap way to do so,
but Airdrops also attract many people just for the profits.
Twitter, Telegram and the web are full of bots and crawlers who are looking for this &amp;quot;free money&amp;quot; to get as many people
on board as possible.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;span id=&quot;continue-reading&quot;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From a projects perspective you don&#x27;t want to attract these people.
Instead you want to incentivise to get involved with your project.
For this reason NEAR Protocol also regularly launches Hackathons, which attract developers who want to build on their platform.
A Smart Contract capable blockchain is only as good as its projects.
If you fail to onboard developers, your project might fail overall in the end.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Airdrops generally launch before an Initial DEX Offering (IDO), so that enough people know about the project and what it is about.
We see an Airdrop as a good opportunity to also find people, who actually want to get involved with us,
so we will launch an Airdrop with a twist.
We will also launch an IDO on &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;skyward.finance&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Skyward Finance&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;,
because we think that they found a way to launch an IDO as fair as possible.
If you don&#x27;t yet know much about the SHRM token, you should read about our &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;whitepaper.shroomkingdom.net&#x2F;6_Token_Economics.html&quot;&gt;Token Economics&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Airdrop is heavily inspired by &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;kanaria.rmrk.app&#x2F;&quot;&gt;RMRK&#x27;s Kanaria NFT launchpad&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.
Instead of giving free tokens, we want people to get their hands dirty and help us doing the advertisement.
The more people you bring to our platform, the more you get rewarded.
For this purpose we will launch a special kind of founder NFT, which will only be available during the
initial Airdrop launch phase of the project.
Once this time is over, there won&#x27;t be any way to acquire new NFTs of this kind ever again,
but the founder NFT will also be tradeable at some point.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get the founder NFT, you will have to do several tasks:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;answer some quiz questions&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;connect your &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;wallet.near.org&#x2F;&quot;&gt;NEAR wallet&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;follow us on &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;twitter.com&#x2F;shrm_kingdom&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;retweet our future pinned post on Twitter&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;like our future pinned post on Twitter&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;join our &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;discord.gg&#x2F;SPZsgSe&quot;&gt;Discord server&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All these requirements will automatically be checked by our Airdrop application, that we still have to develop.
We are also working together with artists to give the NFT a nice looking.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once the NFT has been acquired, you will get a referral link that you can share.
Everytime some else acquires an NFT as well, you will get a referral point.
We also make sure, that you keep following and retweeting the pinned post, otherwise you will lose eligibility
to get referral points.
The NFT will have super powers which will unlock the more referral points you acquired.
We have not yet 100% decided how they will look like, but to give you a general idea here are some thoughts:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;0 referral points: you will unlock the &lt;a rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;near-chan.github.io&#x2F;&quot;&gt;NEAR chan&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; in-game skin once the game launches on mainnet&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 referral point: you will get some SHRM token&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 referral points: you will get x% lifetime bonus for all acquired SHRM tokens within the game&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;...?&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember that you will only have this opportunity once in your life during the NFT Airdrop launch event.
Since we still need to work on the Airdrop application and are looking for artists to help us,
we cannot yet announce the date for this event, but we will keep you updated, so make sure to follow our social media accounts!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
